

OMEZIE STANLEY

Innovative Developer | Machine Learning & Robotics Enthusiast | Forex & Synthetics Trader

About Me

A multifaceted Computer Science graduate with a deep passion for technology and innovation. Specializing in web and app development, machine learning, and robotics (Arduino), I bring a diverse skill set that includes software analysis, hardware repairs, computer assessment in cybersecurity, forex trading, and Proficient graphic design. multiple programming languages and tools, I am driven to create impactful solutions through technology and continuous learning.

- +234-816
 - +234-8167111734, +234-9158256901
- \boxtimes
 - szubby10@gmail.com
- pipeline jiwa,FCT-ABUJA

LANGUAGE

- Python ,C, HTML, CSS, Kotlin
- Forex and Synthetics Trading

EXPERTISE

- Web Application Development
- App Development
- Machine Learning
- Robotics (Arduino)
- Vulnerability Assessment
- Graphics Design (Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator)
- Forex & Synthetics Indices Trading
- Computer Hardware & Software Repairs.

EXPERIENCE

App Developer Freelancer 2020 - 2023

- Designed and developed mobile applications using Kotlin (with some Java).
- Deployed apps to platforms, ensuring performance and security.
- Integrated API services and ad placements within apps for monetization.

Graphics Designer Freelance 2020 - Till Date

- Created visually compelling designs using Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator.
- Designed logos, brochures, websites, and UI/UX elements.
- Worked closely with clients to meet specific design needs.

Forex & Synthetics Trader Self-employed 2022 - Till date

- Analyzed market trends, economic indicators, and executed profitable trades.
- Specialized in forex and synthetic indices trading.

Machine Learning Developer Veritas University Abuja Freelance 2023 - Till date

- Developed and deployed machine learning models for predictive analysis and developed web applications
- Conducted data preprocessing, feature engineering, and model tuning.

Robotics Developer (Arduino) [Freelance, Veritas University 2022 - Till date

- Designed and programmed Arduino-based robotics systems.
- Integrated sensors and actuators to develop responsive robotics solutions.

Web Application Developer Self-employed (freelance) 2022 - Till date

- Designed and developed web applications using python (Django and flask frameworks) with html and css.
- Deployed web apps to platforms, ensuring performance and security.
- Integrated API services and ad placements within apps for monetization.

SKILLS SUMMARY

Meb Development 85%

Machine Learning 90%

App Development 70%

Graphics Design 80%

Forex & Synthetics Trading

Robotics (Arduino) 95%

EDUCATION

Veritas University Bwari - Abuja

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science 2020-2024

CERTIFICATIONS

- Cisco Certified: Python Programming
- Cisco Certified: Cybersecurity Essentials
- Udemy Certified: Machine Learning
- Udemy Certified: Advanced Python Programming